Guide to the Jewish Heritage Foundation of North Carolina Records, 1750-2014 and undated RL.10159
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Exhibits, events, and projects, 1908-2012 and undated; 2; 9.7 Linear Feet; 36.8 Gigabytes
  - Down Home, 1995-2012 and undated; 1
    - [Down Home Exhibit - Publicity], 2002-2012 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Down Home Development Meeting - Charlotte, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - [Down Home Script Outline], 2003 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Duke/UNC/JHF Collab, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Film Discussion, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - SJHS Grant Appl., 2003 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Winslow Feasibility Study - DH, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - [Down Home exhibit], 2003, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Glass/Musleah (Hadassah), 2003, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Down Home - digital promotional material, 2003-2008 and undated; 479 Files; 2.6 Gigabytes
      These digital files include posters, brochures, powerpoint presentations, newsletters, and other promotional material related to the Down Home campaign. Also present are digital image files used to produce promotional material. File formats include. doc, .pdf, .ppt, .indd, .jpg, and .tif.
    - Campaign Strategy, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Center for Doc St, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - [Down Home Campaign Regional Organizational Model], 2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Marcy Cohen Ferris, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Educ Curric, 2004 and undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - [Images used in Down Home book], 2004 and undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - [Down Home] - Script, 2004, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Prospects S-T, 2004, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Exhibit Conceptual, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - [Down Home - Greensboro fundraising], 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Prospects F-L, 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Prospects M-R, 2004-2007 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Exhibition Concept Planning, 2004-2009; 1 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Exhibition Concept Planning, 2004-2009; 2 of 2 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Beth Israel - Fayetteville, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Down Home Logo/Banner, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Educ Curric - Resources, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Film Subjects, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Irene Morris, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Legislature, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Letter of Agreement, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Mid Year Appeal, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - NC Echo, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Outreach to Rabbis, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Tell Us A Story, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Vince, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Down Home exhibit design - digital material, 2005-2006; 26 Files; 1.7 Gigabytes
      These digital files include artists' renderings of exhibit spaces and banners.
    - [Down Home Exhibit - Drafts], 2005, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - DH Education, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Exhibition Walk Through, 2005-2008 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - [Down Home Brochures and Programs], 2005-2011 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Down Home events - digital photographs, 2005-2011; 879 Files; 2.9 Gigabytes
      These digital files include photographs taken at Down Home exhibit openings, receptions, fundraisers, and other events in Charlotte, Durham, Greensboro, and Raleigh.
    - Annual Appeal, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - [Charlotte Hunt Dinner], 2006 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Current Donor Lists, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Down Home Donors, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Education, circa 2006 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Offerman, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - PBS, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Project Plans - [Down Home], 2006 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Triad, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Triangle, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - [Down Home - miscellaneous correspondence], 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Educ Curric - 4th, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Educ Curric - Discussion, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Glaxo Smith Kline, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Greensboro Federation, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - New Leads, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Proforma Application, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - [Triangle Hunt Dinner], 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - DH Photo Permissions, 2006-2010 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - [Down Home correspondence], 2006-2011 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Cannon Foundation, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - [Down Home - Charlotte Fundraising], 2007 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Educ Curric - 8th, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Educ Curric - The Case, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - NC Museum of History, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Shooting Schedule, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - [Down Home] Book Proposal, 2007, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - [Down Home Collections Database printout], 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - [Down Home Exhibit], 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Venue Ltrs of Int. DPI Ltr, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - [Down Home publicity], 2007-2012 and undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Book, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - DH - Greensboro - Exhibit permanent home, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - [Down Home] - Artifacts To Do, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - [Down Home book contract], 2008 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - [Down Home exhibit narrative outline], 2008 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - [Down Home Phase One Submittal], 2008 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Exhibit - Community, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Film Discussed, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Film - Publicity, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Judea Reform Member List, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - [Report on the Book Manuscript of Down Home: Jewish Life in North Carolina], 2008 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Down Home Exhibit, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Down Home marketing, 2008-2009; 1 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Down Home marketing, 2008-2009; 2 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Exhibit, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - [Down Home - Phase Two Submittal, Logo Designs, Preliminary Exhibit Sketches and Analysis of Design Precedent], 2008-2009 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - [Correspondence - publication of Down Home book], 2008-2010 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Down Home book design - digital material, 2008-2010; 71 Files; 903.2 Megabytes
      These digital files include images used in Down Home (book) chapters 1-4 and cover design files.
    - Down Home Recipes, 2008-2010 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Exhibit Scripts, 2008-2010 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - [Draft - Down Home], 2009; 1 of 3 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - [Draft - Down Home], 2009; 2 of 3 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - [Draft - Down Home], 2009; 3 of 3 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - [Down Home] copy editing, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Down Home - Permissions for Book, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - [Down Home - Phase Three Submittal, Exhibit Renderings, Graphic Language Logo Designs], 2009 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - [Down Home - Phase Four Submittal, Exhibit Renderings], 2009 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - [Down Home - Phase Five, Graphic Template and Logo], 2009 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - [Down Home - Phase Five Submittal, Structural Package], 2009 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Film - Ltrs of Interest, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - [Page proofs - Down Home manuscript], 2009 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - [Down Home - miscellaneous], 2009-2011 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Charlotte Federation, 2009-2012 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - AJS Grant, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - DH - Reviews, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - DH - Teacher's Guide, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Docent Guide, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - [Down Home exhibit construction documents], 2010 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - [Down Home - Exhibit Advertising Brochure, Exhibit Status List], 2010 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - [Down Home - Phase Six, Laminate Schedule, Paint Schedule, Graphics Package], 2010 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - [Down Home - Phase Six, Structural Set], 2010 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - [Down Home - recipes from visitors, 2010; 1 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - [Down Home - recipes from visitors, 2010; 2 of 2 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Down Home Reviews/Publicity, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - [Publication of Down Home book], 2010 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Talks - Asheville Powerpoint, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Talks - DH - NCSU, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Federation Proposal, 2010-2011 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Appeal letters, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - DH - Harvard, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - [Down Home - Greensboro Opening Event], 2011 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - [Down Home - Greensboro Print Materials], 2011 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - [Down Home - recipes from visitors - Greensboro], 2011 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - [Down Home Teacher's Guide], 2011 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Greensboro Opening Info, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Mr. Mabry, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Submitted Proposals DCH, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Talk - Richmond, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Treasurer Report, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Cape Fear Museum - DH Exhibit, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Donor Related, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Down Home Teaching Materials, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Beth Jacob Ark, undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Down Home Donor's List, undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - [Down Home Exhibit], undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Down Home Exhibit items to return to owners, undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - [Down Home exhibit - Log of Permissions, Releases and Contents], undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Down Home Exhibit Components List, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - [Down Home Flexible Exhibit Design], undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Down Home responses - "What do you believe are today's most pressing equal rights issues?"], undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - [Down Home Questionnaire], undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - [Down Home voice over for opening credits], undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - [Draft - Down Home: Jewish Life in North Carolina], undated; 1 of 4 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - [Draft - Down Home: Jewish Life in North Carolina], undated; 2 of 4 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - [Draft - Down Home: Jewish Life in North Carolina], undated; 3 of 4 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - [Draft - Down Home: Jewish Life in North Carolina], undated; 4 of 4 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Exhibit - Artifacts, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Gallery Funders, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Ideas for fundraising letter, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - [Legacy Heritage Jewish Studies Project Grant Application], undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Ramsey Library - UNC Asheville, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Standard Presentation, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Synagogue email list, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Talks - Charlotte Panel, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Other exhibits, events, and projects, 1908-2011 and undated; 2
    The materials in this subseries describe various Rosenzweig/JHFNC exhibits and events at the Rosenzweig Gallery and throughout North Carolina including the exhibits "Migrations," "The Running Stag," and "What We Brought With Us: Mementos of the Flight From Europe 1933 to 1950" (also known as the Ucko Exhibit); and the annual art shows at the Rosenzweig Gallery. It also contains materials related to the monograph "An Extended Family: A History of Temple Emanu-El, Weldon, North Carolina" (also known as the Weldon project).
    The series contains postcards, typescripts, correspondence related to grant funding efforts, promotional material, photographs of exhibit objects and events, and background research materials. Digital materials in the subseries include digital photographs of Rosenzweig Gallery art show submissions, exhibits, and events, and digitized photographs and historical documents used for the Migrations exhibit and Weldon project.
    The folders in this subseries are arranged loosely alphabetically by exhibit/event/project and chronologically thereafter.
    Digital material related to Migrations can also be found in the Down Home subseries, as many digital photographs originating with the Migrations project were copied and reused for the Down Home project. Historical records related to Temple Emanu-El in Weldon, NC are located in the North Carolina Temple and Synagogue Historical Collection.
    - Amulet Exhibit, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - [Photographs - The Artist, The Bible The Storyteller - Bourguignon Exhibit], 1994 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Photographs - Bourguignon Sketches, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - [Exhibit - "Call to Conscience: The Life and Times of Rabbi Efraim Rosenzweig"], 2003 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - [Efraim and Marian Rosenzweig Judaica and Hebraica Exhibit], 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Photographs - Gimesh Exhibition [From Morocco to Manhattan], 2001 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - From Russia With Love, Returned Loan Objects, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Russian Exhibit, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Russian Jewish Exhibit, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Russian Jewish Exhibit, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - [Exhibit - Holy Transmitters: Portraits of the Mekubalim (Jewish Mystics)], 1997 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Holy Transmitters: Portraits of the Mekubalim, Lilly Library, Duke, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Jewish Mystics - Lilly Library, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Jewish Mystics Exhibit, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - [Photographs - Homelands Booksigning/DAFFF Exhibit], 2001 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Jewish-Arab Cross Cultural Encounters, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - [Photographs - Third Annual Reception Rosenzweig Museum of the Jewish Family - Jewish-Arab Cross-Cultural Encounters], 1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - [Treasures of the Jewish Family in the Efraim and Marian Rosenzweig Judaica and Hebraica Museum], 1995 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Rosenzweig Gallery events and exhibits - digital photographs and other material, 1997-2009; 193 Files; 290.8 Megabytes
      These digital files include photographs of artwork, gallery displays, and receptions held at the Rosenzweig Gallery. Also included are PDF posters and mailings used to publicize exhibits and events, as well as digital photographs and other materials related to presentations and lectures.
    - [The Museum of the Jewish Family and Rosenzweig Gallery events], 1998 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - [Rosenzweig Museum exhibits and events], 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - JHFNC/Rosenzweig [Event Postcards], 2001-2011 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Travelling Exhibits - JHF/Rosenzweig, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Rosenzweig Gallery juried art shows - digital photographs and other material, 2004, 2006-2009; 286 Files; 432.4 Megabytes
      These digital files mainly consist of digital photographs (.jpg and .tif formats) of submissions and displays of art for the juried art shows held at the Rosenzweig Gallery in 2004 and 2006. Also included are a small number of submission forms and other text relating to the shows.
    - JHF/RG 4th Annual Jewish Art Exhibit Sale, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Kanof Exhibit - Israeli Commemorative Medals, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - [Photographs - Kanof Exhibit of Israeli Commemorative Medals], 1994 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Klezmer, 1999, 2003, 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Kostroma, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - [Exhibit - Maps of the Holy Land], 2006 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - NCHC [North Carolina Humanities Council] Grants, 1992, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Grants [Migrations], 1994-2004 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Grant Sources [Migrations], 1995-1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - [Brochure - Migrations], 1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Migrations, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - [Migrations], 1998, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Museums - Regional - [Migrations], 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Migrations, 1998-2000; 1 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Migrations, 1998-2000; 2 of 2 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Dan Gottlieb - [Migrations], 1999 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Donor Fundraising - [Migrations], 1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Migrations Panels, [1999] (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - The Chosen Land, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Budget - [Migrations], 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Letters - [Migrations], 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Publicity - [Migrations], 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Migrations exhibit - digital images and other material, 1999-2003 and undated; 681 Files; 7.8 Gigabytes
      These digital files include digitized photographs and historical material used in the research and design of the Migrations exhibit. Also included are a small number of text documents containing versions of the exhibit text. Other digital images and other materials that were originally created for Migrations werereused for the Down Home project and are filed in the Down Home subseries under "Down Home research - digitized photographs, historical documents, and other digital material."
    - [Migrations Exhibit], 2000 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - [Migrations Exhibit], 2000 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - The Rosenzweig Museum JHFNC, Migrations: Jewish Settlers of Eastern North Carolina Condition Report Notebook, 2000; 1 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - The Rosenzweig Museum JHFNC, Migrations: Jewish Settlers of Eastern North Carolina Condition Report Notebook, 2000; 2 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - The Rosenzweig Museum JHFNC, Migrations: Jewish Settlers of Eastern North Carolina Condition Report Notebook, 2000; 3 of 3 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - [Color photographs - Migrations Artifacts], circa 2000 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - [Typescript - Migrations: A History of Durham-Chapel Hill Jewish Community], circa 2000; 1 of 4 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - [Typescript - Migrations: A History of Durham-Chapel Hill Jewish Community], circa 2000; 2 of 4 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - [Typescript - Migrations: A History of Durham-Chapel Hill Jewish Community], circa 2000; 3 of 4 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - [Typescript - Migrations: A History of Durham-Chapel Hill Jewish Community], circa 2000; 4 of 4 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Photographs - Migrations Tours, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Evaluations - [Migrations], 2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - NCHC [North Carolina Humanities Council] Final Evaluation - [Migrations], 2001 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Greensboro Historical Museum - [Migrations], 2002 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Mission Statements, 2004 and undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - [Durham - Chapel Hill Jewish Community History Project], undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Durham Questionnaire, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - [35 mm slides - "Peace to Your Bones"], circa 2000s (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - [Exhibit - Picturing the Holy Land in Nineteenth Century Engravings and Lithographs], 2002 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - [Photographs - Picturing the Holy Land in Nineteenth Century Engravings and Lithographs], undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - [Photographs and 35 mm slides - Rattner prints], 1996 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - [Rattner Exhibit at the Blumenthal Jewish Home], 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - [Photographs and 35 mm slides - Scrolls of Fire, Dan Reisinger Exhibit], 2002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - [Steve Heller - CD], 2010 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - DVD - Synagogue Project Bar/Bat Mitzvah, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - [Exhibit - "The Meaning of Light in the Jewish Tradition"], 1997 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - [Photographs - Exhibit "The Meaning of Light in the Jewish Tradition"], 1997 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - The Meaning of Light in the Jewish Tradition, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - The Meaning of Light in the Jewish Tradition - Loan Agreements, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - The Meaning of Light in the Jewish Tradition - Reception, Publicity, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - [Israeli and Polish Stamps], 1945, 1997 and undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - The Running Stag - Culture Nature, 1969-1995 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - The Running Stag - Archaeology, 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - [Background materials for The Running Stag Exhibit], 1997-1998 and undated; 1 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - [Background materials for The Running Stag Exhibit], 1997-1998 and undated; 2 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Stamp Show - Perkins, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - [Exhibit - The Running Stag: Images of Israel in Postage Stamp Art], 1998 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Photographs - Running Stag Exhibit, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Photographs - The Running Stag, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - [Running Stag Exhibit], 1998 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - The Running Stag Exhibit (Fred Hertz Stamp Collection) Perkins Library, Duke, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - The Running Stag - General Info and History of the Exhibit, circa 1998 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - The Running Stag - Sports, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Durham Public Library, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - The Shabbat Exhibit, Durham Public Libraries, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - [Weldon - miscellaneous research materials], 1908, 2006 and undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Weldon - Farber, 1910, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Weldon - Kittner, 1915-1917 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Weldon - Liverman/Marks, 1954-1973, 1990-2006 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Weldon - Israel, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Weldon - Temple Emanu-El Rabbis, 1955-1958, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Weldon - Novey, 1956, 1963, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Weldon Temple, 1962, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Weldon - Bloom, 1966, 1981-2006 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Weldon - Community News - AJTO, 1968-1969, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Weldon - Roanoke Rapids Cemetery, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Weldon History, 1987, 2002 and undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Weldon - Temple Emanu-El Closing, 1997-2006 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Weldon Correspondence, 1999-2007 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Weldon - Kehillah, 2003-2004 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Weldon - Addresses, 2004-2007 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Weldon - Book Contact, 2004-2007 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Weldon - Cohen, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Weldon - digital images and audio file, 2000, 2004-2007; 209 Files; 2.4 Gigabytes
      These digital files include photographs and scanned images related to Weldon, as well as Whitakers and other nearby towns. Locations represented include Temple Emanu-El and Bloom Store. A scan of a Weldon Sabbath School program (1926), and 1 audio file (.aif format) related to Harry Kittner are also present.
    - Allsbrook, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Weldon Contact, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Weldon - Josephson, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Weldon Oral History - [notes], 2006 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Weldon - Silvester, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - [Drafts - An Extended Family: A History of Temple Emanu-El in Weldon, North Carolina], 2007 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - [Draft - An Extended Family: A History of Temple Emanu-El in Weldon, North Carolina], circa 2007 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - [Draft - An Extended Family: A History of Temple Emanu-El in Weldon, North Carolina], circa 2007 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - [Draft 6 - An Extended Family: A History of Temple Emanu-El in Weldon, North Carolina], circa 2007 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - [Temple Emanu-El, Weldon background research material], 2007 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Weldon Copyright, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - [Correspondence related to "A History of Temple Emanu-El], 2007-2009 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - [Color photographs - Temple Emanu-El, Weldon], undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Weldon census, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Weldon notes, circa 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - [Weldon] - Questionnaire, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Guest Book - Ucko, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Ucko Exhibit - Advance Publicity, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Ucko Exhibit - Fanmail, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Ucko Exhibit Duke - Sketches for Brochure, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Ucko Exhibit - Inventory - Check-in, Check-out, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Ucko Exhibit - Loan Agreement Forms, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Ucko Exhibit - Perkins Library Duke, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 41)